Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
か わいいですね
Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
緊張してるんだ
Do you know what we're going to do today?
今日何するかって知ってる?
I don't know.
知らないです
What, a lie?
え、嘘?
You know what we're about to do, right?
さっき何するか知ってるでしょ?
What are you doing here at the love hotel?
ここラブホテルで何してますか?
Erotic things.
エロいこと
oh yeah.
そうそう
Yes, it is.
あってます
I'll do something erotic and film the Suidokai and show it to the whole world.
エロいことして、水道会撮って 全世界に公開しちゃうけど
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
No problem.
問題 ないです
no problem?
問題ない?
Can I wait a moment?
ちょっと待っていい?
yes.
はい
She's a summer kind of girl.
夏って感じの女の子だね
Does it feel like summer?
夏って感じですか?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, you don't like it?
あ、嫌だ?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
The back side is shaking.
後ろ側がぐわんぐわんしてる
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Can you go to the back?
後ろに行ける?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Because I want to take it all in.
全身とりたいから
Ah, nice, nice.
あ、 いいねいいね
It's cold there, isn't it?
そこ寒いでしょ?
That's fine.
そこら辺でいいよ
Look at your smartphone.
スマホの方見て
Well then, let's take our clothes off right away.
じゃあもう 早速脱いでいきましょうか
Oh, can I take it off?
あっ、脱いでいいんですか?
Yeah, that's fine.
うん、いいですよ
Do you want to take it off?
脱ぎたいの?
How much do you want to take off?
どこまで脱ぎますか?
That's it.
そこまで
It's fine on that desk.
その机の上でいいよ
Put your hair back.
髪の毛後ろにして
She's incredibly slender.
すごいスレンダーだね
Are you slender?
スレンダーですか?
Yeah.
うん
Look here.
こっち見て
Can I lower my legs?
足を下げてもいい?
feet?
足?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, are you curious?
あ、気になるの?
be on one's mind.
気になる
be on one's mind?
気になる?
be on one's mind.
気になる
I'm curious.
気になるんだ
How many cups are there?
何カップあるの?
I wonder what it is.
何だろう
Like G?
Gとか?
There's a G.
Gあるんだ
perhaps.
多分
Turn your back a little?
ちょっと後ろ向ける?
behind?
後ろ?
Yeah.
うん
Show me your butt.
お尻見せて
Keep your hair back and front.
髪の毛後ろ前にしてください
Then please look forward.
じゃあ前向いてください
Put your hair back.
髪の毛後ろにして
Because I can take off my bra.
ブラジャー取れるから
Come on, I'll load it up here like this.
ちょっとさあ、ここで こうやって積んであげる
I'll stack it like this.
こうやって積んであげる
Is this so?
こうですか?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Please stick your butt out.
お尻突き出してください
Can I take your pants down?
パンツ下ろしていい?
That's probably what's on it.
多分、あれがついてます
Is it on?
ついてる?
Yes, it's on.
そう、ついてる
I feel like I wore it too.
着けたのも着た気がする
Oh, what about folded sheets?
あ、折り物シートのこと?
Please stretch your legs.
足伸ばしてください
Before, before.
前の、前の
picture?
え?
What is this?
何これ?
picture?
え?
They say it comes with a folding sheet.
折り物シートついてるって言うから
I didn't ask you to introduce yourself.
自己紹介してもらってなかったね
A little bit here, in front and far away, facing straight ahead.
ちょっとこっち、前と遠く、正面と向いて
picture?
え?
What would you like me to do for you today?
今日何てお世話したいですか?
Today is As.
今日は アズ
Az-chan?
アズちゃん?
I'm 25 years old.
25歳です
What is this?
何これ?
Folded sheet.
折り物シート
What kind of records and foundations will be released?
何の記録、 基盤出るんだけど
What is this?
何これ?
The base comes out.
基盤出る
基 盤出る
Because I got one right.
一つ当たってるから
Can you put your hands behind your back?
手、後ろにできる?
On top of that, do this, knee, go in there.
そこの上でこうやってさ、 膝、あっちに入る
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
The hands are really nice.
手、やっぱいいね
Have them bring their hands behind their heads.
両手を 頭の後ろに持ってきてもらおう
That's amazing.
すごいね
You can leave it open.
開いておらせていいよ
It's already a little damp.
もう ちょっと湿ってるよ
Yuzu-chan.
ゆずちゃん
It can get damp.
湿っていける
Why did you draw it?
なぜ描いちゃったの?
Can I lick it a little?
ちょっと舐めていい?
You can lick it.
舐めていい
Can I lick it?
舐めていい?
Yeah.
うん
Lick it properly.
ちゃんと舐めて
Didn't you get it right?
上手く取れてなかったの?
You don't have to laugh, there.
笑わなくていいよ、そこ
It makes me laugh too.
笑 っちゃうのも
It makes me laugh.
笑っちゃう
Then, at the end, can I ask you to reverse the M-shaped turn?
じゃあ最後、M字回逆してもらっていい?
yes.
そう
Spread your legs a little more and show me your boobs.
もうちょっと足広げて、おっぱい見せて
Shall I put my hair back?
髪の毛後ろにしようか
Can you tell the truth?
ほんまを広げられる?
From here this way.
ここからこうやって
Well then, thank you for your help today.
じゃあ今日よろしくお願いしますね
please.
お願いします
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
good?
いい?
What is your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何ですか?
My favorite food is white rice.
好きな食べ物は 白米です
White rice?
白 米?
Do you like it alone?
単体で好きなの?
I like it alone.
単体で好きです
Do you like rice balls?
おにぎりとか好きなの?
My favorite onigiri is salt musubi.
おにぎりは塩むすびが一番好きです
Oh, seriously?
あ、マジ?
Are you satisfied with the size of your breasts?
おっぱいの大きさ満足してますか?
Because it was getting smaller.
小さくなってたから
Have you lost weight?
痩せたの?
I lost weight.
痩せました
Ah, there it is.
あ、そこなんだ
Then turn your back?
じゃあ後ろ向ける?
Do it in front of your hair.
髪の毛前にしてね
Is there a type of man you like?
好きな男性のタイプとかあるんですか?
Who do you like?
好きな人?
Mild.
マイルドで
He's quite a good-looking guy.
結構イケメン系だね
I like cool faces.
かっこいい顔が好き
Eh.
えー
So let's move forward?
じゃあ前向ける?
So what is your second favorite food?
じゃあ2番目に好きな食べ物は何ですか?
My second favorite food is...
2番目に好きな食べ物は...
It's carbonara.
カルボナーラです
Carbonara.
カルボナーラ
Yes, it's gotten bigger.
そう、大きくなったよ
Did it progress?
進 行しましたか?
Kind and gentle.
優しく優しく
Kindly, kindly, kindly.
優しく優しく優しく
I'm sure you'll talk.
きっと喋ってもらおう
き っと喋ってもらおう
Let's do it like this.
こうやってもらおう
Well, let's make fun of it.
じゃ、からけちゃいましょう
Let's finally get it in.
やっと入れてもらおう
oh.
お ー
Okay, let me put some effort into it.
はーし、力を入れてもらおう
Make your case cool.
ケースをかっこよくして
Let me put my foot down.
足をかけてもらおう
Let me put my hands behind my back.
手を後ろに手つけてもらおう
Come on, come on, just leave it as is for now.
さあさあさあ、最初そのままでいいよ
Let's turn your body back.
体を後ろにしてもらおう
Turn your body back
体を後ろにしてもらお
cormorant.
う
Let me hold both legs.
両 足持ってもらおう
Come on, come on
さあさあさ
a.
あ
While pushing, have them apply more force.
押 しながら結局で力を入れてもらおう
Turn to this side.
こっち側向けて
It's cute.
かわいいね
Lise-chan, let's put that in.
リーズちゃん、それ入れてみようか
a,
あ、
I was able to do it.
でき た
Oh, you made it?
あ、できた?
Hold it down to two.
2つと押さえておいて
This side
こ っち 側向
Kete.
けて
Ah, done.
あ、 できた
Boil that a little.
そ こ を、 ちょっとゆ
It's Kurida.
っ くりだ
It's out.
出しですよ
Put it in slowly.
ゆっくりゆっくり入れて
Come on, come on.
さあさあさあ
Lise-chan, let's put that in.
リーズちゃん、それ入れてみようか
a,
あ、
I was able to do it.
でき た
Oh, you made it?
あ、できた?
I was able to do it.
できた
Hold it down to two.
2つと押さえておいて
There,
そこを、
It's fun to take it slow, right?
そ こを、 ゆっくりが楽しいでしょ?